<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Project on Discussions on r/politics</title><link>https://lassesofus.github.io/Political_discussions/</link><description>Recent content in The Project on Discussions on r/politics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://lassesofus.github.io/Political_discussions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Data Description</title><link>https://lassesofus.github.io/Political_discussions/data-description/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lassesofus.github.io/Political_discussions/data-description/</guid><description>During this project, we worked with three data sets
Submissions from the r/politics subreddit mentioning &amp;ldquo;Trump&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Biden posted between 10-01-2020 and 11-2-2020. The comments sections of the above submissions. Polling data obtained from FiveThirtyEight. In the following, we will describe these datasets and give an overview of their most important properties.
1. The Submissions Visitors at r/politics will quickly notice that the majority of the submissions posted on the site are by users linking to news articles published on news media sites like CNN or The Huffington Post.</description></item><item><title>Network analysis</title><link>https://lassesofus.github.io/Political_discussions/network-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lassesofus.github.io/Political_discussions/network-analysis/</guid><description>Building the network In order to model the social interactions of the users with one another, we constructed an undirected network where all nodes were the authors. We then created reciprocal edges such that each edge represented that the two authors had replied to each other’s comment or reply at least once. Afterwards we assigned an edge weight based on the total number of replies or comments the two authors had written to one another, and added the inferred political conviction of each author as a node attribute in the network.</description></item><item><title>Text analysis</title><link>https://lassesofus.github.io/Political_discussions/text-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lassesofus.github.io/Political_discussions/text-analysis/</guid><description>The U.S. elections are one of the most observed international events, as they affect and influence different countries’ policy-making approaches and economies. Hence, various hidden aspects of elections are drawn out and analyzed using sentiment analysis, but it also has limitations; for example, it is hard to recognize sarcasm trivially. In some cases, the negative sentiments are classified as positive due to the writing styles employed. Note, the project does not cover these shortcomings.</description></item></channel></rss>